A non-empty zero-indexed array A consisting of N numbers is given. The array is sorted in non-decreasing order. The absolute distinct count of this array is the number of distinct absolute values among the elements of the array.

For example, consider array A such that:

  A[0] = -5
  A[1] = -3
  A[2] = -1
  A[3] =  0
  A[4] =  3
  A[5] =  6
The absolute distinct count of this array is 5, because there are 5 distinct absolute values among the elements of this array, namely 0, 1, 3, 5 and 6.

Write a function:

int solution(int A[], int N);

that, given a non-empty zero-indexed array A consisting of N numbers, returns absolute distinct count of array A.

For example, given array A such that:

  A[0] = -5
  A[1] = -3
  A[2] = -1
  A[3] =  0
  A[4] =  3
  A[5] =  6
the function should return 5, as explained above.

Assume that:

N is an integer within the range [1..100,000];
each element of array A is an integer within the range [−2,147,483,648..2,147,483,647];
array A is sorted in non-decreasing order.
Complexity:

expected worst-case time complexity is O(N);
expected worst-case space complexity is O(N), beyond input storage (not counting the storage required for input arguments).
Elements of input arrays can be modified.