Write a function:

class Solution { public int solution(int[] A); }

that, given a non-empty zero-indexed array A of N integers, returns the minimal positive integer (greater than 0) that does not occur in A.

For example, given:

  A[0] = 1
  A[1] = 3
  A[2] = 6
  A[3] = 4
  A[4] = 1
  A[5] = 2
the function should return 5.

Assume that:

N is an integer within the range [1..100,000];
each element of array A is an integer within the range [−2,147,483,648..2,147,483,647].
Complexity:

expected worst-case time complexity is O(N);
expected worst-case space complexity is O(N), beyond input storage (not counting the storage required for input arguments).
Elements of input arrays can be modified.