A zero-indexed array A consisting of N integers is given. A triplet (P, Q, R) is triangular if it is possible to build a triangle with sides of lengths A[P], A[Q] and A[R]. In other words, triplet (P, Q, R) is triangular if 0 ≤ P < Q < R < N and:

A[P] + A[Q] > A[R],
A[Q] + A[R] > A[P],
A[R] + A[P] > A[Q].
For example, consider array A such that:

  A[0] = 10    A[1] = 2    A[2] = 5
  A[3] = 1     A[4] = 8    A[5] = 12
There are four triangular triplets that can be constructed from elements of this array, namely (0, 2, 4), (0, 2, 5), (0, 4, 5), and (2, 4, 5).

Write a function:

int solution(int A[], int N);

that, given a zero-indexed array A consisting of N integers, returns the number of triangular triplets in this array.

For example, given array A such that:

  A[0] = 10    A[1] = 2    A[2] = 5
  A[3] = 1     A[4] = 8    A[5] = 12
the function should return 4, as explained above.

Assume that:

N is an integer within the range [0..1,000];
each element of array A is an integer within the range [1..1,000,000,000].
Complexity:

expected worst-case time complexity is O(N2);
expected worst-case space complexity is O(N), beyond input storage (not counting the storage required for input arguments).
Elements of input arrays can be modified.