Two positive integers N and M are given. Integer N represents the number of chocolates arranged in a circle, numbered from 0 to N − 1.

You start to eat the chocolates. After eating a chocolate you leave only a wrapper.

You begin with eating chocolate number 0. Then you omit the next M − 1 chocolates or wrappers on the circle, and eat the following one.

More precisely, if you ate chocolate number X, then you will next eat the chocolate with number (X + M) modulo N (remainder of division).

You stop eating when you encounter an empty wrapper.

For example, given integers N = 10 and M = 4. You will eat the following chocolates: 0, 4, 8, 2, 6.

The goal is to count the number of chocolates that you will eat, following the above rules.

Write a function:

class Solution { public int solution(int N, int M); }

that, given two positive integers N and M, returns the number of chocolates that you will eat.

For example, given integers N = 10 and M = 4. the function should return 5, as explained above.

Assume that:

N and M are integers within the range [1..1,000,000,000].
Complexity:

expected worst-case time complexity is O(log(N+M));
expected worst-case space complexity is O(log(N+M)).